Guide to the Pierson College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1964-2012 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Pierson College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1964-2012 maintained by the dean
1961-2012
RU 256
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
139.25
(211 Boxes)
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Pierson College, Yale University.
Pierson College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-J-1 (YRG 13-J-1), Records of the dean of Pierson College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically by Class year, thereunder alphabetically by student name.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Pierson College, Yale University.
College students; Pierson College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student Records for the Class of 1964, Accession 19ND-A-305
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 1965, Accession 1971-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 1966, Accession 19ND-A-304
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 1967, Accession 19ND-A-306
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
  - Freshman Counselor Reports, November 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 1968, Accession 19ND-A-308
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2044
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 1969, Accession 19ND-A-307
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Classses of 1970-1975, Accession 1980-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2051
  - Class of 1970
  - Class of 1971
  - Class of 1972
  - Class of 1973
    - Class of 1973, general, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1974
    - Class of 1974, general, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1975
    - Class of 1975, general, 1971-1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Student records for the Class of 1975-1978 (impounded), 1971-1978; Accession 1975-A-015; 3.5; (4 boxes)
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
- Student records for the Class of 1976, Accession 1981-A-039
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - Commencement 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Class of 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
  - College Credits (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 1977, Accession 1982-A-035
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  - Ex-1977
- Student records for the Class of 1978, Accession 1983-A-062
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - Ex-1978
- Student records for the Class of 1979, Accession 1984-A-039
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  - Ex-1979
- Student records for the Class of 1980, Accession 1985-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - Non-Degree
- Student records for the Class of 1981, Accession 1987-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Non-degree
- Student records for the Class of 1982, Accession 1988-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1983, Accession 1989-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Ex-Students
- Student records for the Class of 1984, Accession 1990-A-029
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - Ex
- Student records for the Class of 1985, Accession 1991-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - Ex-students
- Student records for the Class of 1986, Accession 1992-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1987, Accession 1993-A-003
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1988, Accession 1994-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1989, Accession 1997-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1990, Accession 1998-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - Withdrawn
  - Deceased
- Student records for the Class of 1991, Accession 1999-A-004
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
- Student records for the Class of 1992, Accession 2000-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
- Student records for the Class of 1993, Accession 2003-A-001
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
- Student records for the Class of 1994, Accession 2003-A-011
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Classes of 1995-1999, Accession 2003-A-124
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Class of 1995
  - Class of 1996
    - Ex-Students:, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Class of 1997
    - Ex-Students:
  - Class of 1998
    - Ex-Students:
  - Class of 1999
    - Ex-Students:
- Student records for the Class of 2000, Accession 2006-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2001, Accession 2006-A-060
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2002, Accession 2006-A-061
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - Withdrawals
  - Deceased
- Student records for the Class of 2003, Accession 2006-A-222
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2079
- Student records for the Class of 2004, 2000-2004; Accession 2009-A-027
  - Did Not Complete
- Student records for the Class of 2005, 2001-2005; Accession 2010-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2081
- Student records for the Class of 2006, Accession 2012-A-010
- Student records for the Class of 2007, 2003-2007; Accession 2013-A-009
  Restricted until January 1, 2082
- Student Records for the Class of 2008, Accession 2014-A-077
  Restricted until January 1, 2083
- Student Records for the Class of 2009, Accession 2016-A-004
  Restricted until January 1, 2084.
- Student Records for the Classes of 2010 and 2011, Accession 2017-A-007
  Restricted until January 1, 2087
  - Class of 2010
  - Class of 2011
- Student Records for the Class of 2012, Accession 2018-A-006
  Restricted until January 1, 2088